

NHẬT HUY ĐOÀN

Frontend Developer

- Male
- +84 364051835
- nhathuy97ars@gmail.com
- Oanang, Vietnam
- i https://fb.com/topcv.vn

OTHER SKILLS

- Can read Document and Requirements fast and efficiently
- Always has an urge in researchingand learning efficient ways toapproach the problems.
- Critical Thinking
- Research
- Time Management
- Teamwork



I'm a Frontend Developer. I'm extremely passionate about web development especially Frontend Development, helping businesses and improve their online presence. In the past, I have studied Automation Engineering at Danang University of Science and Technology (2015 - 2020). Now I have finished Frontend Development Course at CyberSoft Academy and had nearly 1 year of working experience in ReactJS. Now I currently aim to learn as much as I can in a work environment and to further my own abilities in a professional setting.



EDUCATION

DANANG UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

SEP 2015 - MAY 2020

Major: Automation Engineer

level: Good

CYBERSOFT ACADEMY

SEP 2015 - MAY 2020

Major: Frontend Developer

level: Good



TECNICAL SKILLS

• Programming Languages:

- Java, Javascript ES6

• Frameworks/Libraries/Techs :

- HTML, CSS (SASS)
- ReactJS, Redux, Redux-Thunk
- NodeJS, ElectronJS
- Java Core, Spring MVC
- MySQL, Mongoose
- Git, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Canva

• Foreign Languages:

- English (Reading, Speaking, Listening)

Soft Skills:

- Presentation skills
- Teamwork
- Technical communication
- Highly adaptable



WORK EXPERIENCE

EPC SOLAR

JUNE 2020 - JUNE 2020

Electic Engineer

Main responsibilities:



BOOKING MOVIE

APR 2022 - APR 2022

Front-end Developer

Customer

Cybersoft Center

Description

- · Booking Movie Tickets Website.
- Link website: http://tmovie.surge.sh
- Link source: https://github.com/nthanhtung9x/cinema_project

Member

1

Role

- Analyze , design layouts website.
- Process the logic proficient.
- $\hbox{\bf \cdot} \ \, \text{Improve performance website: lazyloadComponent, useMemo, useCallback,}... \hbox{\bf Technology} \\$
- Front-end: HTML, CSS, ReactJS, Axios, AntDesign, Redux, Redux Thunk, Sweetalert, Slick Slider,...



Build website with React JS by F8 Academy

2022

Frontend Developer by Cybersoft Academy

2022